Guide to the Union Settlement Association records,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series IV: Fundraising
  - Foundations (D), 1936-37, 1942-49 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Foundations (E), 1944-48 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Foundations (F), 1932, 1940-47 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Foundations (G), 1932, 1942-48 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Foundations (H), 1921-48 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Foundations (I-K), 1941-47 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Foundations (L), 1942-49 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Foundations (M), 1932-37, 1941-47 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Foundations (N-O), 1932, 1943-47 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Foundations (P), 1932-33, 1942-48 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Foundations (R), 1942-49 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Foundations (S), 1941-51 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Foundations (T), 1941-47 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Foundations (U-V), 1943-46 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Foundations (W), 1942-48 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Joint Supplementary Fundraising Committee, 1947 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Music Benefits, 1942-44 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Theater Benefit, 1948-49 (Box 23, Folder 11)
- Series V: William Kirk Files
  - American Friends Service Committee, 1964-65 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Amherst College, 1961-67 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Building, 1956 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Carnegie Hill Neighborhood Project, 1961-63 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Carnegie Hill Neighborhood Project, 1964-66 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Census and Statistical Reports, 1964-65 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Citizens Advice Bureau, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - City Planning Commission, 1969 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Colby College, 1966-68 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - College Readiness, 1963-67 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - College Readiness, 1968-70 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Community College-East Harlem, 1967-68 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Community Development Agency, 1966-68 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Community Organizations, 1961-69 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Community Service Society, 1953-64 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - "Construction for Progress,", 1968 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Consumer-Farmer Milk Cooperative, Inc., 1963-69 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Consumers Union, 1957-62 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1950-58 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1962-65 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1966-67 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1968-69 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Leonard Covello Senior Center of East Harlem, 1965-69 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Credit Union, 1965-69 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Carver Children's Center, 1958-67 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1961-70 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Day Care Council of New York, 1962, 1965-67 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Leggett Memorial Children's Center, 1964-69 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Pleasant Avenue, 1969 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Supervision of Programs, 1964 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Union Negotiations, 1966-68 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Washington Houses, 1960-67 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Directories of East Harlem, 1964-65 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - East Harlem Community Corporation, 1967-71 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - East Harlem Council for Community Planning, 1955, 1958-60 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - East Harlem Council for Community Planning, 1961 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - East Harlem Council for Community Planning, 1962 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - East Harlem Council for Community Planning, 1963 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - East Harlem Council for Community Planning, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - East Harlem Council for Community Planning, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - East Harlem Council for Community Planning-Committees, 1957-60 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - East Harlem Council for Community Planning-Committees, 1961 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - East Harlem Council for Community Planning-Committees, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - East Harlem Council for Community Planning-Committees, 1963-64 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - East Harlem Credit Unions, 1966-67 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - East Harlem Cultural Committee, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - East Harlem Day Center, 1961-64 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - East Harlem Good Neighbor Committee, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - East Harlem Interfaith Community Services, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - East Harlem Project, 1960-62 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - East Harlem Project, 1963-64 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - East Harlem Project, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - East Harlem Public Housing Association, 1963, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - East Harlem Skills Training Center, 1967-69 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - East Harlem Study Club, 1962-September 1963 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - East Harlem Study Club, October 1963-64 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - East Harlem Study Club, 1965-68 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - East Harlem Summer Festival, 1960-62 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - East Harlem Summer Festival/Youth Council, 1963-67 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - East Harlem Tenants' Council, 1964-68 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - East Harlem Triangle, 1966-67 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - East River Area Rehabilitation, 1966-67 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - East River Area Services Program, 1952-67 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - East River Urban Renewal, 1961-64 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - East River Urban Renewal, 1965-68 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Federation of Protestant Welfare Agencies, 1953, 1962-68 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Foundations, 1965-69 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Franklin Plaza, 1960 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Franklin Plaza, 1961 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Franklin Plaza, 1962 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Franklin Plaza, 1963 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Franklin Plaza, 1964 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Franklin Plaza, 1965 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Franklin Plaza, 1966-68, 1970 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Financial Statements, 1962 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Financial Statements, 1963-65 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - "Franklin Plaza Independent,", 1962-64 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - "Franklin Plaza Independent,", 1964-65 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Information Bulletin, 1964 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Minutes, 1960-62 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - "News,", 1961-62, 1965-66 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Nursery School, 1961-64 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Statement of Closing of Title and of First Mortgage Loan, 1965 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Frawley Circle Project, 1965-66 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Gaylord White House, 1958-59 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Gaylord White House, 1960-65 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Gaylord White House, 1966-70 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Getzoff Proposal, 1964 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Good Neighbor Week, 1962 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Greater New York Fund, 1963-64 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Greater New York Fund, 1965-66 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Greater New York Fund, 1967 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Greater New York Fund-Correspondence, 1963-69 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Harlem Advisory Board, 1967-69 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Head Start, 1965-66 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Hellgate Project, 1962-65 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Housing-Urgent Cases, 1963-69 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    [RESTRICTED ]
  - James Weldon Johnson Community Centers, Inc., 1963-68 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - JOIN, 1963-66 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Junior League, 1962-64 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Legislators-Correspondence, 1962-67 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Ellen Lurie, 1955-57 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Ellen Lurie, 1958-65 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Manhattan School, 1966-68 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Kate Maremont Foundation, 1965-66 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Mental Health Programs, 1965-66 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - National Council of Churches, 1965-67 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - National Federation of Settlements, 1961-65 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - National Federation of Settlements, 1966-69 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Neighborhood Vitality, 1961-66 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Neighborhood Youth Corps, 1964-69 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - New York City Board of Education, 1958-67 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - New York City Council Against Poverty, 1966-67 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - New York City Housing Authority, 1961-68 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - New York Medical College, 1962, 1966-68 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - New York Times, 1960, 1962 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - 104th Street, 1968-69 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - 106th Street Committee, 1964-65 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - 114th Street Rehabilitation Project, 1965 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Park Avenue Market, 1960-65 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Photo Training Program, 1968-69 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Police, 1966-69 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Proposed Old Age Center, 1956-59 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Regional Planning Association, 1964-68 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Ruppert Brewery Site, 1965-68 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Schools, 1960-66 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Senior Citizens, 1960-65 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - "Settlement and Political Activities,", 1961 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Sheffield Project Incorporated, 1964-68 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Steering Committee, 1969-71 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Thrift Shop, 1962-66 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Union Negotiations, 1952-56 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Union Theological Seminary, 1958, 1960-65 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - United Neighborhood Houses, 1961-63 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - United Neighborhood Houses, 1964-66 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - United Neighborhood Houses, 1967-69 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Volunteers, 1965-66 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Washington Houses, 1954-63 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Washington Houses, 1964-69 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Washington Legislative Conference, 1961-66 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - World's Fair, 1963-64 (Box 38, Folder 8)
- Series VI: Alber Mayer Files
  See also "Series VIII - Audio-Visual Materials"
  - Block Development Project, 1965 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1968-77 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence-Union Settlement, 1960-76 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - "East Harlem-The Possibilities,", 1976 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Franklin Plaza, 1961-64 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Park Avenue Market, 1974 (Box 39, Folder 6)
- Series VII: Programs and Services
  - Activities Council, 1949-53 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Adult Education, [nd] (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Adult Literacy, 1994 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Art Workshop, 1950-54 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Camp-Activity Reports, 1952 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    [RESTRICTED]
  - Camp-Bazaar, 1953-57 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Camp-Children's Records (A-B), 1945-57 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Camp-Children's Records (C), 1949-57 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Camp-Children's Records (D-E), 1945-57 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Camp-Children's Records (F), 1950-56 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Camp-Children's Records (H-M), 1955-57 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Camp-Children's Records (R), 1950-58 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Camp-Correspondence, 1947-51 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Camp-Correspondence, 1952 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Camp-Correspondence, 1953-55 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Camp-Correspondence, 1956-58, 1964 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Camp-Dance Benefit, 1950 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Camp-Film, 1944-49 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Camp-Promotional, 1950's (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Camp-Publications, 1948-49 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Camp-Reports, 1948-53 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Cancer Detection Clinic, 1955-58 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Children's Program, 1956-58 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - City of New York Youth Board, 1958, 1966-70 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Co-ed Program, 1950-52 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - College Readiness, 1963-95 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - College Summer Service Group, 1947-52 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - College Summer Service Group, 1953-54 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Consumer Education, 1944 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Consumer Study Action Program, 1962-68 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Credit Union, 1957-94 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Day Camp, 1955-62 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Day Camp-Reports, 1958 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Day Care-Administration, 1950-64 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Day Care-Children (A), 1950-55 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Day Care-Children (A), 1950-55 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Day Care-Children (A), 1950-55 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Day Care-Children (B-C), 1950-55 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Day Care-Children (D-G), 1950-55 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Day Care-Children (L), 1950-55 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Day Care-Children (M-P), 1950-55 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Day Care-Children (R), 1950-55 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Day Care-Children (R), 1950-55 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Day Care-Children (R), 1950-55 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Day Care-Children (S-W), 1950-55 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Day Care-Registration Cards, c. 1955 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - East Harlem Day Center, 1958-62 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - East Harlem Day Center, 1963-65 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - East Harlem Day Center, 1966-69 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - East Harlem Day Center-Financial Reports, 1954-64 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - East Harlem Legal Services Program, 1968 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Alice in Wonderland, 1951-52 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Angora Juniors, 1950-51 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Arcadians, 1951-52 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Black Orchids, 1950-51 (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Blazons, 1953-54 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Cobra Queens, 1953-54 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Colts, 1951 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Colts Juniors, 1951-51 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Demons, 1953-54 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Devils, 1951-54 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Devolettes, 1950-51 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Dragonettes, 1953-54 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Dramatic Club, 1950-51 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Earth Angels, 1954-55 (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Flying Saucers, 1951-52 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Glamazons, 1951-52 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Golden Nymphs/Velveteens, 1951-52 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Hawks, 1950-51 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Hawks, 1950-52 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Hawk Debs, 1951 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Kinglets, 1951-52 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Knights, 1951-52 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Latin Aces, 1951-52 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Merry Maids, 1950-51 (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Militant Juniors, 1953-54 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous-Boys, 1945-55 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous-Girls, 1950-56 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Ocelots, 1950-52 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Open Group, 1949-50 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Paragons, 1950-51 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Play Group, 1955 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Question Marks, 1950-51 (Box 58, Folder 8)
    [RESTRICTE]
  - Ranger Juniors, 1950-51 (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Rebel Debs, 1954-56 (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Red Devilettes, 1953-55 (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - Sapphires, 1949-50 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Settlers, 1950-51 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Velours, 1951-52 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Vigilantes/Royal Capries, 1954-55 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Royal Juniors, 1953-55 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Royal Queens, 1950-51 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Royal Shields, 1952-53 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Saint Edwards, 1950-51 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Whoosie Whatsies, 1953-54 (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Wolves, 1949-50 (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Evening Program, 1950-51 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Head Start: Committee of Concerned Parents, 1966-69 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Head Start: Correspondence, 1965-66 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Head Start: Correspondence, 1967 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Head Start: Correspondence, 1968-69 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Head Start: Federation of Independent Head Start Centers, 1966-68 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Head Start: Follow-up Program, 1966 (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - Head Start: Proposals and Contracts, 1965-68 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Head Start: Reports to Parents, 1967 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Head Start: Title I, 1966-68 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Hotline, 1972-74 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Hungry Club, 1968-71 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous Announcements and Memos, 1901-95 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Music School, 1947-72 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Neighborhood Center for Block Organization, 1948 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Neighborhood Youth Project, 1957-60 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Neighborhood Youth Project, 1961-62 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Neighborhood Youth Project, 1963-64 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Neighborhood Youth Project-Financial Statements, 1957-63 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Nursery School-Wilhelm Weinberg, 1960-64 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Performing Arts, 1967-73 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Play Group Reports, 1955 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Pre-Teen Delinquency Project, 1960-63 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Pre-Teen Delinquency Project, 1964-65 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Pre-Teen Delinquency Project-Cases, 1962 (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - Program Director Correspondence, 1953-58 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - School Age Department-Group Records, 1950-52 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - School Age Department-Teacher Conferences, 1950-52 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Sports Team Evaluations c., 1956 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Sunnyside Day Nursery, 1941-46 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Sunnyside Day Nursery-Annual Reports, 1901-1941 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Tuesday Lounge, 1950-51 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Upward Bound, 1966-69 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Young Adult Committee, 1950-51 (Box 45, Folder 9)
- Series VIII: Audio-Visual Materials
  - Board of Directors, 1950, 1955-56, (photographs) (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Building, ca.1900-1930, ca. 1960 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Camp Nathan Hale, ca., 1900, 1940s, 1990s (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Camp Ellen Marvin, ca., 1920, 1943, 1950 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Camp Gaylord White, ca., 1950 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Children, ca., 1900-90s (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Christmas Party, ca. 1960s (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Metro North, 1960s (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous, ca. 1900-90 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Performances, 1926, 1950s, 1990s (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Programs, 1940s-90s (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Seniors, 1950s-60s (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Settlement House Centennial, 1986 (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Sports, 1898-1970s (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Staff, 1930s-90s (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - Teens, 1960s-90s (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - Washington Houses, 1960s (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - Winter Carnival, 1950 (Box 46, Folder 18)
- Series IX: Oversize Materials
  - Camps, 1950s, (Photographs) (Box 302, Folder 1)
  - Children, 1940s-70s, (Photographs) (Box 302, Folder 2)
  - Exhibit-Children's Programs, 1960s-70s, (Photographs) (Box 303)
  - Exhibit-Children's Programs, 1960s-70s, (Photographs) (Box 304)
  - Exhibit-Children's Programs, 1960s-70s, (Photographs) (Box 305)
  - Miscellaneous, 1950s-70s, (Photographs) (Box 302, Folder 3)
  - Neighborhood Scenes, 1960s, (Photographs) (Box 306)
  - Programs, 1970s-80s, (Photographs) (Box 302, Folder 4)
  - Seniors, 1980s, (Photographs) (Box 302, Folder 5)
  - Teens, 1940s-80s, (Photographs) (Box 302, Folder 6)
  - Bazaar, [nd], (Posters) (Box 302, Folder 7)
  - Camp Nathan Hale, 1904-24, (Scrapbooks) (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Camp Nathan Hale, 1904-1926, (Scrapbooks) (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Franklin Plaza, 1958-59, (Blueprints) (Box 1)
  - Franklin Plaza, 1958-59, (Blueprints) (Box Tuber Box 2, Folder 2)
  - George Washington Houses, 1962, (Drawings--Albert Mayer) (Box Tuber Box 3)
  - 250 East 105th Street, [nd], (Drawings--Albert Mayer) (Box 3)
  - Gaylord White House, 1, 1959, (Drawings--Albert Mayer) (Box 3)
  - Park Avenue North, 1962, (Drawings--Albert Mayer) (Box 4)
  - Pedestrian "Main Street" from Lexington to Third Avenues, 1966, (Drawings--Albert Mayer) (Box 4)
  - James Weldon Johnson Houses, 1961-64, (Drawings--Albert Mayer) (Box 4)
  - Metro North Plaza Apartments, 1965, (Drawings--Albert Mayer) (Box 4)
  - Project Linkage, East 118th Street, 1994, (Drawings) (Box 5)
  - Skills Training Center, 1971, (Drawings) (Box 6)
  - Blake Hobbs Park, 1976, (Drawings) (Box 6)
  - 304-14 East 103rd Street, 1966-67, (Drawings) (Box 7)
  - Union Settlement Apartments, 305 East 105th Street, 1964-67, (Drawings) (Box 8)
  - Union Settlement Apartments, 305 East 105th Street, 1967, (Drawings) (Box 9)
  - East Harlem, 1960s, (Maps) (Box 10)
  - Metro North Redevelopment, 1965-68, (Maps) (Box 11)
  - Blake Hobbs, 1960s, (Photographs) (Box 12)
  - Lexington Planning Coalition, [nd], (Posters) (Box 13)
  - Hotline Conference, [nd], (Posters) (Box 13)
  - Aerial View, East Harlem, [nd], (Posters) (Box 13)
  - East Harlem Plaza, 1962, (Mounted Posters) (Box 13)